<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<News>
    <NewsPiece>
        <Title>SpaceX's Next Starship Prototype Taking Shape</Title>
        <ImgUrl>https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/gLAiKfmDHWuzNpo5TeSLe4-1200-80.jpg.webp</ImgUrl>
        <Content>Construction of the test craft is proceeding apace, as two new photos posted on Twitter today (Sept. 17) by company founder and CEO Elon Musk reveal.</Content>
    </NewsPiece>
    <NewsPiece>
        <Title>NASA's Juno Mission Cheks Out Eclipse on Jupiter</Title>
        <ImgUrl>https://cdn.images.express.co.uk/img/dynamic/151/750x445/1338443.jpg</ImgUrl>
        <Content>All is well on our largest neighbor; NASA's Juno spacecraft just managed to spot the shadow of Jupiter's moon, Io, passing over its marbled clouds.</Content>
    </NewsPiece>
    <NewsPiece>
        <Title>Europe Wants Ideas for Cave-Spelumking Moon Robots</Title>
        <ImgUrl>https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/8X7AGzgNVb86gk9Sbn8xYo.jpg</ImgUrl>
        <Content>As NASA makes a big push to land humans on the moon's surface by 2024, the European Space Agency (ESA) wants to learn more about the lunar caves that lie beneath.</Content>
    </NewsPiece>
    <NewsPiece>
        <Title>Antimatter responds to gravity like Einstein predicted, major CERN experiment confirms</Title>
        <ImgUrl>https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/X6Vo7rSnpj7wWAg2J8pHv7-1920-80.jpg.webp</ImgUrl>
        <Content>This result marks the first-ever direct observation of free-falling antimatter, in which atoms are made of antiprotons instead of protons and antielectrons (positrons) instead of electrons.</Content>
    </NewsPiece>
    <NewsPiece>
        <Title>The artist who sculpted the 4-dimensional fabric of space and time</Title>
        <ImgUrl>https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/vz8KGTvSnPecEaMAUoPGLR-1920-80.jpg.webp</ImgUrl>
        <Content>This distorted block wasn't transported to our planet from the depths of outer space, however; it comes from the mind of Ashley Zelinskie, whose mission it is to take elusive intricacies of the cosmos and turn them into fine art. </Content>
    </NewsPiece>
    <NewsPiece>
        <Title>Why Venus is now a slim crescent and will disappear from the evening sky this weekend</Title>
        <ImgUrl>https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/Rtzx9iNQmXwocgWF2wKhEE-1920-80.jpg.webp</ImgUrl>
        <Content>You may have noticed in recent weeks that the planet Venus has slipped from the post-sunset sky, slimming into a crescent shape as it drops from view. Its reign as the bright "Evening Star" in 2023 is over, as a relatively rare celestial phenomenon takes shape.</Content>
    </NewsPiece>
    <NewsPiece>
        <Title>Satellites reveal how deadly Morocco earthquake moved ground</Title>
        <ImgUrl>https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/sjnTk5x3c2rLY2NV4rvxcM-1200-80.jpg.webp</ImgUrl>
        <Content>Satellite measurements have revealed the extent of ground movement caused by the 6.8-magnitude earthquake that struck Morocco last week, killing nearly 3,000 people. </Content>

    </NewsPiece>
    <NewsPiece>
        <Title>Why is Neptune's moon Triton so weird?</Title>
        <ImgUrl>https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/9CFrjRcjekBi36nVmqN9PB-1200-80.jpg.webp</ImgUrl>
        <Content>Sometimes, astronomy is like a forensic investigation: We can't just rerun the past, so we have to study clues to figure out what happened. And the outer solar system contains one striking crime scene holding a big mystery: How the environment around Neptune got a moon like Triton.</Content>
        
    </NewsPiece>
    <NewsPiece>
        <Title>Alien mummies in Mexico? NASA's UFO study team says don't bet on it</Title>
        <ImgUrl>https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/chmxs72HQgcQjYfZGsHCPc-1200-80.jpg.webp</ImgUrl>
        <Content>UFOs and aliens are once again in the headlines this week.
Unfortunately, this is not because a mothership landed on the White House lawn, but because NASA released a long-awaited report published by the independent study.</Content>
    </NewsPiece>
    
</News>